# ANTHONY PURIFICATO

### WEB DEVELOPER

**8**48-345-8911

✓ apurificato5680@gmail.com

Keyport, NJ

linkedin.com/in/apurificato/

github.com/apurificato

### PROFILE

Detail-oriented professional focused on web development and software programming. Primary experience in Front-End technologies: HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Experienced in CSS Frameworks (like Bootstrap) and React JS. Continuing advancement with back-end tools including Node.js, SQL/NoSQL, and Python.

## SKILLS/TOOLS

- HTML, CSS, Javascript
- Bootstrap (CSS Frameworks)
- React JS
- Node JS
- WordPress
- SEO Audits & Scans
- Copywriting
- Email Marketing
- MailChimp & Campaign Monitor
- Zoho Projects Platform

### CERTIFICATIONS

#### **FULL STACK PROGRAMMING**

**Rutgers Coding Bootcamp**June 2024

### **RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN**

freeCodeCamp

#### 2021

### EXPERIENCE

#### **Solar Mite Solutions**

Oct. 2022 - Present

### DIGITAL MARKETING/WEB SPECIALIST

- Wordpress website maintenance and SEO support.
- Customer engagement and building relationships, communicating promotional services and ensuring positive experiences.
- Conducting market research and digital strategy.
- Additional administrative tasks to support office, when additional help is needed.

### **D2** Creative

Jan. 2022 - Oct. 2022

### **DIGITAL PLATFORMS EXPERT**

- Top-performing, lead publisher and expert for CMS platforms.
- Researched platforms, tools, and marketing opportunities that benefit the company, reporting to the Head of Customer Engagement.
- Presented on regular strategy meetings with company leadership.
- Conducted webinars to train project managers on various platforms.
- Work included previous content publishing responsibilities.

### **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF ARTS,
PSYCHOLOGY, WRITING MINOR

**Rutgers University** 

Graduated 2019

### EXPERIENCE

Jan. 2022 - Oct. 2022

#### **DIGITAL CONTENT & MEDIA SPECIALIST**

- Published content for web, email, and digital courses using CMS (WordPress, Joomla, MailChimp, and Articulate Storyline 360).
- Spearheaded launch of blog section and content on internal company website, utilizing SEO best practices to increase traffic.
- Built email templates with MailChimp, Campaign Monitor, and BEE Free platforms using HTML & CSS.
- Designed and led an email marketing drip campaign in MailChimp to promote a white paper.
- Performed SEO site scans and audits, meta content copywriting, and fixed on-site technical and content issues to improve SEO scores for client websites. Used in conjunction with Google Keyword search.
- Researched and culled keywords to use in effort to better Google search results.
- Worked with big name clients in the technical and MedTech space such as Fujifilm (Drupal web redesign project) and CooperSurgical (web publishing/maintenance and regularly creating webpages and email templates using HTML & CSS).